{"quiz_list":[{"id":1,"category":"Education","question":"Asetofintructionsthattellsthecomputerhowtobehave,whattodoandderiveatasolutiontoaparticularproblemis:","answerList":[{"ans":"Algorithm","status":0},{"ans":"Pseudocode","status":0},{"ans":"Programming","status":0},{"ans":"Program","status":1}]},{"id":2,"category":"Education","question":"Asetoflogicallysequencedinstructionsthatallowstofindthesolutiontoaproblemis:","answerList":[{"ans":"Algorithm","status":1},{"ans":"Pseudocode","status":0},{"ans":"Programming","status":0},{"ans":"Program","status":0}]},{"id":3,"category":"Education","question":"Thesixstagesofprogramdevelopmentinlogicalorderare:","answerList":[{"ans":"Define,Analyze,Write,Test,Document,Debug","status":0},{"ans":"Define,Analyze,Develop,Write,TestandDebug,Document","status":1},{"ans":"Define,Write,Develop,Analyze,Test,Document","status":0},{"ans":"Define,Develop,Write,Test,Document,Debug","status":0}]},{"id":4,"category":"Education","question":"Theprogramminglanguagethatisusedtoshowpupilstheconceptandstructureofprogrammingiscalled:","answerList":[{"ans":"Basic","status":0},{"ans":"Cobol","status":0},{"ans":"Pascal","status":1},{"ans":"Java","status":0}]},{"id":5,"category":"Education","question":"Javaisanexampleofwhichgenerationprogramminglanguage:","answerList":[{"ans":"4GLs","status":1},{"ans":"3rd","status":0},{"ans":"2nd","status":0},{"ans":"1st","status":0}]},{"id":6,"category":"Education","question":"Whichofthefollowinggenerationsofprogramminglanguageexecutedcodefaster:","answerList":[{"ans":"4GLs","status":0},{"ans":"3rd","status":0},{"ans":"2nd","status":0},{"ans":"1st","status":1}]},{"id":7,"category":"Education","question":"Algorithmsmustbeallofthefollowingexcept:","answerList":[{"ans":"Logical","status":0},{"ans":"Ambiguous","status":1},{"ans":"Concise","status":0},{"ans":"Precise","status":0}]},{"id":8,"category":"Education","question":"WhichlanguagehadcodessuchasMOV,ADD,SUB?","answerList":[{"ans":"Java","status":0},{"ans":"Binary","status":0},{"ans":"Pascal","status":0},{"ans":"Assembly","status":1}]},{"id":9,"category":"Education","question":"Whichofthefollowinghadexecutesprogrammingcodeslinebyline,ratherthanthewholeprogram:","answerList":[{"ans":"Compiler","status":0},{"ans":"Interpreter","status":1},{"ans":"Executer","status":0},{"ans":"Translator","status":0}]},{"id":10,"category":"Education","question":"Allthefollowingareexamplesofthirdprogramminglanguageexcept:","answerList":[{"ans":"Pascal","status":0},{"ans":"C#","status":1},{"ans":"Basic","status":0},{"ans":"Fortran","status":0}]},{"id":11,"category":"Education","question":"Whichofthefollowingprovidesareusemechanism?","answerList":[{"ans":"Abstarction","status":0},{"ans":"Inheritence","status":1},{"ans":"DynamicBinding","status":0},{"ans":"Encapsulation","status":0}]},{"id":12,"category":"Education","question":"Whichofthefollowingisnotatypeofconstructor?","answerList":[{"ans":"Copyconstructor","status":0},{"ans":"Defaultconstructor","status":0},{"ans":"Friendconstructor","status":1},{"ans":"Parameterizedconstructor","status":0}]},{"id":13,"category":"Education","question":"Whichofthefollowingtypeofclassallowsonlyoneobjectofittobecreated?","answerList":[{"ans":"Abstract","status":0},{"ans":"Virtual","status":0},{"ans":"Singleton","status":1},{"ans":"Friend","status":0}]},{"id":14,"category":"Education","question":"Whathappensifthebaseandderivedclasscontainsdefinitionofafunctionwithsameprototype?","answerList":[{"ans":"Compilerreportsanerroroncompilation.","status":0},{"ans":"Onlybaseclassfunctionwillgetcalledirrespectiveofobject.","status":0},{"ans":"Onlyderivedclassfunctionwillgetcalledirrespectiveofobject.","status":0},{"ans":"Baseclassobjectwillcallbaseclassfunctionandderivedclassobjectwillcallderivedclassfunction.","status":1}]},{"id":15,"category":"Education","question":"Whichofthefollowingoperatorisoverloadedforobjectcout?","answerList":[{"ans":"<<","status":1},{"ans":">>","status":0},{"ans":"+","status":0},{"ans":"=","status":0}]},{"id":16,"category":"Game","question":"HowmanytotalturretsarethereontheSummoner'sRiftmap?","answerList":[{"ans":"22","status":1},{"ans":"20","status":0},{"ans":"24","status":0},{"ans":"18","status":0}]},{"id":17,"category":"Game","question":"Whichchampion'sultimatetemporarilyincreasesthesizeofitstarget?","answerList":[{"ans":"Lulu","status":1},{"ans":"Yasuo","status":0},{"ans":"Nasus","status":0},{"ans":"Chogath","status":0}]},{"id":18,"category":"Game","question":"Whatisthemaximumnumberofchampionsavailabeinonegame?","answerList":[{"ans":"10","status":1},{"ans":"5","status":0},{"ans":"20","status":0},{"ans":"12","status":0}]},{"id":19,"category":"Game","question":"WhatisthenameofRenekton'sultimate?","answerList":[{"ans":"Dominus","status":1},{"ans":"Furyofthesands","status":0},{"ans":"Riteofthearcane","status":0},{"ans":"Lastbreath","status":0}]},{"id":20,"category":"Game","question":"Whichchampiondon'thaveabilitytostealth?","answerList":[{"ans":"Yasuo","status":1},{"ans":"Shaco","status":0},{"ans":"Teemo","status":0},{"ans":"Khazix","status":0}]},{"id":21,"category":"Game","question":"Whatchampionisknownas'TheLadyofLuminosity'?","answerList":[{"ans":"Lux","status":1},{"ans":"Ahri","status":0},{"ans":"Evelynn","status":0},{"ans":"Quinn","status":0}]},{"id":22,"category":"Game","question":"Whosejokesays'Formynexttrick,I'llmakeyoudisappear!'?","answerList":[{"ans":"Shaco","status":1},{"ans":"Zedd","status":0},{"ans":"Yasuo","status":0},{"ans":"Akali","status":0}]},{"id":23,"category":"Game","question":"AtwhatminutecanateamsurrenderonTwistedTreelinemap?","answerList":[{"ans":"15","status":1},{"ans":"20","status":0},{"ans":"16","status":0},{"ans":"10","status":0}]},{"id":24,"category":"Game","question":"Whichchampionhas'anuncontrollablesadness'?","answerList":[{"ans":"Amumu","status":1},{"ans":"Yasuo","status":0},{"ans":"Swain","status":0},{"ans":"Vex","status":0}]},{"id":25,"category":"Game","question":"Whohasthepassiveability'Camouflage'?","answerList":[{"ans":"Teemo","status":1},{"ans":"Yasuo","status":0},{"ans":"Gwen","status":0},{"ans":"Annie","status":0}]},{"id":26,"category":"Game","question":"Howmuchtruedamagetomonstersandminionsdoesthesummonerspell'Smite'doatlevel11?","answerList":[{"ans":"680","status":1},{"ans":"560","status":0},{"ans":"720","status":0},{"ans":"750","status":0}]},{"id":27,"category":"Game","question":"WhenwillthefirstminionsbespawnedfromtheNexus?","answerList":[{"ans":"1:05","status":1},{"ans":"1:15","status":0},{"ans":"1:10","status":0},{"ans":"1:00","status":0}]},{"id":28,"category":"Game","question":"HowlongwillthenextwaveofminionsbespawnedinLeagueofLegends?","answerList":[{"ans":"30","status":1},{"ans":"25","status":0},{"ans":"35","status":0},{"ans":"40","status":0}]},{"id":29,"category":"Game","question":"HowmanykindsofminioninLeagueofLegends?","answerList":[{"ans":"4","status":1},{"ans":"3","status":0},{"ans":"2","status":0},{"ans":"5","status":0}]},{"id":30,"category":"Game","question":"Whatsummonerskillallowsyoutorevealanareaofthemapfor5seconds?","answerList":[{"ans":"Clairvoyance","status":1},{"ans":"Destiny","status":0},{"ans":"Hawkshot","status":0},{"ans":"Heightenedsenses","status":0}]},]}
